007names.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy

007Names, Inc. knows that you care how information about you is shared and we appreciate your faith that we will do so judiciously. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting the 007Names, Inc. website, you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Notice. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact info@007names.com.

## Information We Collect About Our Customers

### Supplied Information:

We store and receive any information entered on our website or provide us through any other means. We utilize this information that you provide to contact you, provide services for you, and respond to your requests.

### Required Information:

We are required by the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), the organization which assumes responsibility for domain name allocation, to collect certain information. This includes: your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, the creation and expiration dates of your domain name, the name server information associated with the domain name, and where available, your fax number.

### Information Provided by Your Browser:

In addition to the above information, our web server collects the following information, automatically supplied by your browser, so that we may better serve you in the future and to analyze demographic trends. This includes: the type of web browser you are using, the page you link from 007names.com, operating system and platform, and Internet Protocol (IP) address. Your IP address is used to study trends, diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.

### Cookies:

We employ the use of "cookies" to help tailor our site to you as well as provide services. Cookies are text files placed by a website on your hard drive allowing us to identify your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookies created by other sites. The purpose of this is to enable us to regulate the online ordering process by preserving the state of your online orders.

## Information We Share

### Required Information:

We are required by ICANN to make available the following required information provided to us during the domain name registration process. This information includes: your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, the creation and expiration dates of your domain name, the name server information associated with your domain name, and where available, your fax number. This information will be publicly available to anyone via a "port 43" WHOIS service. Please note: we may not be able to control how members of the public use the information obtainable via WHOIS.

### Legal Circumstances:

When we are required to do so by law, court order, or any other government agency or to comply with our Service Agreement, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of 007Names, Inc. our users, or others, we may release account and other personal information. 

### Business Transfers:

In the event 007Names, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

## Security: SSL Encryption

We protect your financial transactions by employing the use of Secure Sockets Layer technology, which encrypts the information you send to us via the website. 

## Information Available to You:

In the event of a change or inaccuracy in your user information, we permit you to update your user information by logging in to your account. 

## Links to Other Sites:

007names.com web site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we, 007Names, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

## Children:

007Names, Inc. does not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 18, you may use our services only with the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. 

## Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions:

By choosing to visit our website, www.007names.com, you hereby agree that your visit and any dispute you have regarding the protection of your privacy during this visit is subject to our Disclaimer, this Notice, and our Terms of Agreement, including but not limited to our limitations of liability, disputes, and application of the law of the state of New Jersey. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please send email to info@007names.com and we will attempt to resolve them. Please note that our business changes constantly and so our privacy policy and Terms of Agreement are also subject to change. Any changes are effective immediately upon posting on the 007names.com website. You are responsible for checking our website frequently to keep apprised of recent changes. Use of information that we gather now will be subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. By using our website, you confirm that you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by the terms as stated in this privacy policy.
